<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Inbok Rhee</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Inbok Rhee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Inbok Rhee</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a PhD Candidate at the Department of Political Science, University of California, San Diego. My research focuses on legislative and democratic development in Sub-Saharan Africa. My dissertation investigates the logic of legislator attention in developing democracies and examines when and how some politicians are able to focus more on national policy-making than being mere constituency servants. To answer these questions, I have been conducting extensive fieldwork in Kenya, developing an original dataset on politicians’ career background, conducting qualitative interviews with Kenyan voters and politicians, and analyzing tens of thousands of parliamentary speech texts as data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/home/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/research/</guid>
      <description>Dissertation
Title: Legislator A ention and Democratic Development in Kenya Committee: Karen Ferree (Co-Chair), Clark Gibson (Co-Chair), Scott Desposato, Stephan Haggard, and Molly Roberts
Papers &amp;amp; Presentations
 “Subjective-To-Subjective Link in Economic Voting: Using Afrobarometer Data.” Under Review. Presented at the Annual Western Political Science Association (WPSA) Conference. March 2016. “Diversity, Institutions, and Politics: Explaining the Distribution of Public Services in South Africa.” with John Porten and Clark Gibson. Working Paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Winter 2018
 Section Instructor. POLI11 Introduction to Comparative Politics (Professor Karen Ferree) Graduate Student Mentor. POLI198RA Research Apprenticeship  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>/rhee_cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rhee_cv/</guid>
      <description>I embed a current version of my CV below. You can also download the PDF here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>POLI11: Introduction to Comparative Politics (Winter 2018)</title>
      <link>/poli11_winter2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poli11_winter2018/</guid>
      <description> Sections (SEQUO 147)  Fridays 09:00 - 09:50 am Fridays 10:00 - 10:50 am   Section Slides  Week 1: Janurary 12  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opinion Polls and the Kenyan Presidential Election - 2</title>
      <link>/oldpost/opinion-polls-and-the-kenyan-presidential-election-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/oldpost/opinion-polls-and-the-kenyan-presidential-election-2/</guid>
      <description>Continuing with the series, I took a look at the 2013 opinion polls and tried to compare it to the actual election returns. All data come from the Wikipedia page on the 2013 elections. As before, I used only the data points which at least provided the sample size and the survey duration.
Trends As before, I start with the overall time trends. The overtime plot shows Uhuru rapidly narrowing the gap with Raila.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opinion Polls and the Kenyan Presidential Election - 1</title>
      <link>/oldpost/opinion-polls-and-the-kenyan-presidential-election-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/oldpost/opinion-polls-and-the-kenyan-presidential-election-1/</guid>
      <description>It’s five days to the election, and I’ve been playing a little bit with the opinion poll data for the 2017 Kenyan Elections. To the best of my abilities, I have collected the data from newspaper articles and the releases from major survey firms. I’ve only used surveys that were at least trying to be somewhat nationally representative, and those which included some basic details about the surveys including the total number of respondents or the survey period.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>